<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.downloadmanager.SickPotatoHead"
       name="SickPotatoHead"
       version="1.6.9"
       provider-name="lsellens">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script"
             library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service"
             library="service.py">
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">SickPotatoHead is a Metapackage which combines SickBeard, Couchpotato and Headphones in one Addon built from SABnzdb-Suite</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">SickPotatoHead is een metapackage wat Sickbeard, Couchpotato en Headphones combineerd in één add-on gebouwd vanuit SABnzbd-Suite</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">SickPotatoHead est un méta-paquet qui combine SickBeard, Couchpotato et Headphones en un seul add-on construit depuis SABnzdb-Suite.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">SickPotatoHead é um Metapacote que combina o SickBeard, Couchpotato e Headphones num único Addon construído a partir da SABnzdb-Suite</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">SickPotatoHead é um pacote que combina SickBeard, Couchpotato e Headphones em um único addon construído do SABnzdb-Suite</summary>
    <summary lang="es">SickPotatoHead es un \"Metapaquete\" el cual combina SickBeard, Couchpotato y Headphones en un solo Addon construido a partir de SABnzdb-Suite</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">SickPotatoHead és un \"metapaquet\" el qual combina SickBeard, Couchpotato i Headphones en un sol Addon construït a partir de SABnzdb-Suite</summary>
    <summary lang="de">SickPotatoHead ist ein Metapaket  das SickBeard, Couchpotatoe und Headphones in einer Erweiterung vereint.</summary>
    <summary lang="hy_am">SickPotatoHead-ը Metapackage է, որը միավորում է SickBeard-ը, Couchpotato-ը և Headphones-ը SABnzdb-Suite-ից ստեղծված մեկ լրացման մեջ</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">SickPotatoHead jest metapakietem, który łączy w całość SickBeard, Couchpotato i Headphones, dodatek zbudowany jest z SABnzdb-Suite</summary>
    <description lang="en">SickPotatoHead is a fork of SABnzbd-Suite geared toward us unfortunate enough not to have newsgroups access. Updated frequently to newest versions of SB, CP, and HP.</description>
    <description lang="nl">SickPotatohead is een afsplitsing van SABnzbd-Suite gericht op ons die jammer genoeg niet tot nieuwsgroepen toegang hebben. Regelmatig bijgewerkt naar de nieuwste versies van SB, CP, en HP.</description>
    <description lang="fr">SickPotatoHead est un fork de SABnzbd-Suite destiné à vous qui n'avez malheureusement pas assez d'accès aux newsgroups. Mis à jour régulièrement vers les nouvelles versions de SB, CP, et HP.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O SickPotatoHead é uma derivação da SABnzbd-Suite, destinada aos menos afortunados que não possuem acesso a newsgroups. É actualizado frequentemente para as versões mais recentes de SB, CP, and HP.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">SickPotatoHead é uma revisão do SABnzbd-Suite. Atualizado frequentemente com as novas versões de SB, CP e HP.</description>
    <description lang="es">SickPotatoHead es un fork derivado de SABnzbd-Suite orientado a los que como nosotros no tenemos acceso a grupos de noticias. Se actualiza frecuentemente a las últimas versiones de SB, CP, y HP.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">SickPotatoHead és un fork derivat de SABnzbd-Suite orientada cap a nosaltres els que no tenim accés a grups de notícies. S'actualitza freqüentment a les últimes versions de SB, CP, i H</description>
    <platform>linux</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
    <source>https://github.com/lsellens/service.downloadmanager.SickPotatoHead</source>
    <news>1.7.0 - update to SickRage-v2017.04.26-1, and CouchPotatoServer-711310d</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
